THE CHARACTERS, INSTITUTIONS,
COMPANIES, AND PLACES
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL
Welcome.
One moment.
Wait here. I'll bring the car over.
Mint chocolate?
Is that spicy?
It's not that spicy.
Shall we…
ULTRA TTEOKBOKKI
It's hot.
- Let's make that.
- Okay.
That looks amazing.
And to kick it up a notch.
All done.
Maybe you have the wrong job.
Why are you so serious about food?
Eating good food is comforting.
Filling your stomach also fills the heart.
Try it.
It's a little spicy.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
I'll bring the car.
GENERAL MEETING GUIDE
Wow.
Good morning.
What's on today's schedule?
EPISODE 4
You have a luncheon at noon
with Global Talent Forum.
A meeting with Director Park
from Gangwoo Chemicals at 2 p.m.
An interview with
Business Magazine at 4 p.m.
What's this?
It's a guide to the Headhunting
Association's general meeting.
If you'd like to attend,
I'll adjust your schedule.
I'm not attending.
REPORT ON ESTABLISHING
HEADHUNTING ACADEMY
Headhunting Academy?
They're to name the academy
after CEO Lee Yong-hoon
- who was the association's president.
- Who?
CEO Lee Yong-hoon.
HEADHUNTING ASSOCIATION
CHAIRPERSON - KIM HYE-JIN
One, two.
As I told you, as a special article
on female CEOs
there will be about 20 pages.
Photos and interviews of seven CEOs
including Ms. Kang will be published.
Hello.
Gosh, Ms. Kim.
You came early.
The previous photo shoot isn't over yet.
- I came early on purpose, so don't worry.
- Okay.
It must be Ms. Kang's photo shoot.
This one looks nice.
Please take good photos of Ms. Kang.
She represents our industry.
Aren't you rivals?
In the female CEO special,
you two are from the same industry.
It was for my own benefit.
"If the one in second is amazing,
the one who comes ahead of second place
would look even better."
Wouldn't people think that?
Ms. Kim, you're unbeatable.
I'd like to participate
in founding the academy.
Why all of a sudden?
Do you still need to mooch off
CEO Lee's glory?
Unless you want me to get involved,
take his name out.
Then I'll stay out of it.
How dare you pretend
to be considerate of his good name.
You're still the one who caused his death.
Do you really think so?
Do you honestly think…
that I have no idea?
Stop dirtying CEO Lee's name.
If you're human and have a conscience.
Let's go, Mr. Yu.
Ms. Kang.
Mr. Secretary.
What's on Ms. Kang's schedule
this weekend?
Yong-hoon's daughter entered
middle school this year.
We're having dinner together.
Join us if you're free.
Mrs. Lee would love to hear from you.
Relax.
Your behavior
makes it obvious
that you killed Yong-hoon.
Please check her schedule and let me know.
Shall we start?
Let's get going.
How about the tteokbokki place?
No, thanks. You can't even eat it.
Let's take a walk.
I can't…
I can't handle spicy food,
but I'm confident at walking.
Why did you suggest walking?
- Pardon?
- I didn't think
we'd walk for 30 minutes in silence.
Then would you like to jog?
Can't tell if he's attentive or not.
Why aren't you asking anything?
I'm sure you have many questions.
I don't want to pry.
Even being asked questions
could be hurtful.
You don't owe me any explanation.
I'll only believe what I see.
Pass it to me!
- Here!
- Over here!
- Pass us the ball!
- Here, please!
- Over here!
- Pass the ball!
- Over here.
- Excuse me!
- It's our ball!
- Over here!
Do you like
basketball?
Whoa, incredible!
That was amazing.
He's fast.
No! Block him!
Over here. No.
Here you go.
- Nice.
- What's that?
Thank you.
Thank you, sir!
You should exercise more.
You can't get exhausted from just that.
Just that?
I played so hard.
You didn't even go easy on me.
Sports are meant to be played fair.
Besides, you told me
not to go easy on you.
It'd be cheap to ask for it.
You just do it without being asked.
That's not right.
That's against the rules.
Is this a match?
An international game? The Olympics?
Do you like winning that much?
Yes, I hate losing.
I want to win at everything.
Then I'll always let you win from now on.
- Really?
- Yes.
- No matter what?
- No matter what.
- You'll let me?
- I'll let you.
That sounds good.
Oh, Eun-ho.
I heard that Ji-yun saw
CEO Kim Hye-jin today.
Did anything happen?
Ji-yun has a long history with Ms. Kim.
It's something you should know
as her secretary.
At Career Way,
Kim Hye-jin was Ji-yun's mentor.
Before what happened to CEO Lee,
Ji-yun looked up to her a lot.
A few years ago,
Career Way was scammed
by a paper company.
WAS CAREER WAY REALLY OBLIVIOUS?
Thinking it was a promising start-up,
Career Way formed a group
of founding members.
It shut down within a few months.
Their goal had been investment fraud.
Career Way had no idea?
That's what they stated officially.
Then Ji-yun was informed that someone
from Career Way was involved in the fraud.
She asked for an investigation,
but CEO Lee Yong-hoon left a will
and committed suicide.
He took the entirety of the blame.
He didn't want things to worsen further.
But that doesn't make it Ms. Kang's fault.
No, of course not.
At that time, they needed a common enemy.
It was perfect
for shifting the public eye.
A traitor who led the CEO to his death
with her whistleblowing.
The case was closed,
Career Way got away without charges,
and at the helm was Kim Hye-jin.
After the situation subsided,
she took over as CEO.
To sugarcoat it,
Ji-yun became independent.
In reality, she was kicked out.
Even I was scared as a bystander.
People's attitudes changed
completely overnight.
Ji-yun endured a lot to get here.
She blamed herself a lot too.
It's not surprising
that her brain is overloaded.
She couldn't rely on anyone getting here.
She had no choice but to get strong.
And that's how she became the invincible
Kang Ji-yun as we know her today.
Hello, Mr. Park.
Did you take a look
at the client's sales analysis?
I made a list of their sales and profits
these past three years.
One moment, please.
I'm sorry. Hold on.
WORLD CORPORATION
PROFIT ANALYSIS
Yes, Mr. Park.
The client obtained the patent
before the competitors, so that's fine.
Then I'll send you the SWOT analysis
of the client and their competitors
by tomorrow morning.
ANALYSIS OF VARIOUS FACTORS
OF A COMPANY
Of course. You should take a close look
before making the decision.
Bye.
Are these data for one project?
Since I became a consultant
from being a researcher,
I haven't gotten any results of my own.
I can't spend all my life
assisting someone.
I want to make this successful
and prove my competence.
I'll make this successful no matter what.
You're doing very well already.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Do it as you always do.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Please, head home.
I've tried it so many times…
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
Did you recommend Mr. Park Geun-ha
to change jobs?
- Let's talk later.
- Okay.
Yes.
Kyung-hwa, how do you know Mr. Park?
Kyung-hwa has been working hard
on him as her candidate.
- Hasn't she contacted him for a while?
- Yes.
What are you talking about?
He didn't mention that on the phone.
At my previous company,
I helped Mr. Park change jobs.
A good position came up,
so when I called him,
he was just ecstatic.
I've been contacting him for a month
regarding the World Corporation case.
World Corporation?
They haven't picked a candidate yet.
You never reported it to me.
Yesterday, he made his decision
to apply to World Corporation
until you called him this morning.
Now, he says he's reconsidering it.
I'm sorry, but I already told him.
He's my candidate whom I contacted first.
I must make this project successful.
World Corporation's JD is strict,
so you know how long it takes
to find the right candidate.
Can't you just let this one go?
It might be easy for you
because you have connections,
but I spent many sleepless nights
on this case.
You think it's easy for me
because I have connections?
How can you say that?!
I had reasons of my own to call Mr. Park.
Let's be brutally honest.
If Mr. Park liked your proposal,
he would have refused mine.
Aren't you forcing
your suggestions on them
to increase your performance?
- Mr. Kim…
- What?!
What's all this fuss about?
Are you saying that both of you
will proceed your project
with this candidate?
Yes.
He's my candidate,
and I contacted him first.
I helped him change his job last time.
He wants to work with me again.
Does any of you think about the candidate?
Keep your personal feelings out of it.
Analyze this with your teammates,
and whoever is better
for the candidate's career
should be in charge.
- Mr. Kim.
- What happened?
Who will be in charge?
Kyung…
Kyung-hwa…
Kyung-hwa, are you crying?
Why is she crying?
Mr. Kim.
Why don't you yield to her this time?
Kyung-hwa worked really hard on it.
She's right.
Kyung-hwa always helps with your work.
She searches for your candidates.
Listen, Mr. Kim.
Just be the bigger man this time
and throw it away like this.
Candidates aren't objects
that you throw away.
Where's the JD for World Corporation?
It should be at Kyung-hwa's desk.
DETAILED JOB DESCRIPTION
FOR AN OPEN POSITION
Since when did you know
that Kyung-hwa contacted Mr. Park?
Did everyone know except me?
So only I didn't know?
Just great.
Just absolutely great.
Mr. Kim, I can explain…
Mr. Yu?
It's really refreshing.
You didn't have to follow me.
I won't be long.
You must feel terrible.
It's not because I don't want to yield.
She didn't follow protocol.
If she had reported it to me,
I wouldn't have called Mr. Park.
I was the only one in the dark.
They all team up on me
and tell me to give it up.
Because Kyung-hwa worked hard.
What about me? Didn't I work hard?
Do I just sit around?
I'm well aware that Kyung-hwa worked hard.
I care about her, too.
Never mind.
It just makes me look cheap.
Why am I even telling you all this?
I can't stand it!
I'll go and tell them off.
Forget it.
It's my fault for being ignored.
Tell Kyung-hwa to take it.
Mr. Park would be better off
at World Corporation.
I'll explain it to him.
Thank you.
Kyung-hwa.
This is the special coffee
usually for our high-maintenance Ms. Kang.
Drink it while it's still warm.
Thank you.
Are you working late again?
I think I made a mistake.
Kyung-hwa.
Mr. Kim may not seem like it,
but he actually cares about you a lot.
Don't worry, and don't be discouraged.
Even if you work late, don't skip dinner.
I'll get going.
Remember the list of tasty restaurants.
I recommend Grandma's Gukbap.
Have a good evening.
What's going on with World Corporation?
Candidate Park Geun-ha has
his final interview to go.
World Corporation has been waiting
to fill this position,
so things are proceeding quickly.
And the candidate?
Right.
Thankfully, he's cooperating with us.
Mr. Kim, did you find another candidate
for the position you offered Mr. Park?
I'm still searching.
I'll find a list of candidates
that fit the JD by this week.
Good.
Try not to overlap this time.
The rest of you can help him
with his search.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Meeting's over.
Mr. Kim, do you need help with the search?
It's okay. I'm sure you're all busy.
Let's go and have lunch.
That sounds good.
Let's go, Kyung-hwa.
I have a lot of work,
so go ahead without me.
- Don't skip lunch, Kyung-hwa.
- Okay.
All right.
What shall we eat today?
Here are the minutes for today's meeting.
Will Team One be okay?
What? Is there a problem?
It still seems awkward
between Kyung-hwa and Mr. Kim.
What's wrong with that?
I feel awkward with all my employees.
Isn't that normal at work?
Do you feel awkward with me?
Of course.
Do you think that we're friends?
Right.
It's unfortunate.
What was that about?
I should bring the kids here later.
It's so delicious.
You're just super hungry.
You must've been nervous.
Meeting with editors
always gives me butterflies.
No matter how many I publish,
I can't get used to it.
By the way, Daddy Yu,
I signed contracts with two more books.
- Really?
- Yup. This will be on me.
You came all the way here. It'll be on me.
I also have to get something to go.
Moist salt bun.
Mocha salt bun only available here.
An egg tart.
And this one's for me.
- Is it the CEO's lunch?
- Yes.
Do you have to get her lunch too?
I don't have to,
but if I don't, she won't eat anything.
She likes bread from this bakery.
She had meetings outside this morning,
so she probably didn't eat anything.
Ms. Kang.
Sometimes, she needs more care than Byeol.
You must have
gotten the hang of things now.
You were a mess at first.
- Does it seem that way?
- Yes.
Is that so?
It's Ms. Kang.
She finished earlier than I thought.
Su-hyeon, I'd better go.
- See you.
- Okay, bye.
I didn't know his boss was a woman.
You probably didn't have lunch,
so here's some bread.
If you don't want--
For your thoughtfulness.
It's hot.
- Hello.
- Isn't it good?
Try some.
- Gosh, Mr. Yu.
- Ma'am.
- Thank you so much for last time.
- You're welcome.
I brought something for you.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
You look amazing.
Work hard.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
What are you looking at?
Mr. Kim and Kyung-hwa.
I was thinking about
how they could make up naturally.
Goodness.
I thought that it was something serious.
For something like this,
just grab a date, have a few drinks,
and things will smooth over.
They don't even eat together.
How would they grab a drink?
- They don't eat together?
- That's serious.
We can make an event
where they have to drink.
- A welcoming party.
- A welcoming party?
A welcoming party?
What welcoming party?
- A welcoming party for Mr. Yu.
- Yes, that's right.
My, my. I did not think of that.
We don't have company dinners
because of a certain someone.
Mr. Yu, I'm sorry for disappointing you.
I was disappointed.
We can't disappoint him!
Okay, let's hold a welcoming party.
Wouldn't that be nice, all around?
Listen, I'm the boss here.
I haven't given my permission yet.
- So you won't allow it?
- We won't hold a welcoming party?
There won't be any welcoming party?
Goodness.
It's up to you, but I won't be there.
Okay as long as I'm out.
But you have to be there…
Okay, I got it.
You can't cancel it, okay?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Lousy company dinner…
Thanks, Daddy Yu.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
THE LATE PARK JAE-HOON
THE LATE JUNG SU-JIN
Su-jin, Jae-hoon, I'm here.
Mom still cries a lot.
Didn't Seo-jun grow up a lot?
He takes after you more and more.
It's unfair.
Don't be so sad
that you can't see Seo-jun.
When he gets a little older
and is able to understand everything,
I promise to bring him with me.
Does it still make you cry
when it's been so long?
Time doesn't heal
the loss of a child.
You just get more bitter.
Wait.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I won.
- I'll win next time.
- Yes, you won.
Seo-jun is having a lot of fun.
Mom, look at this.
Look how big he's smiling.
Let's see who does better.
- Do you find him that adorable?
- Rocks, paper, scissors, shoot!
Don't you regret it?
Of course not. He's my son.
Why would I regret it?
I regret it.
I should have stopped you then.
You aren't even married.
There's no need to bring it up.
It's all in the past.
My daughter is more important
than my grandson.
Your happiness matters
more to me than Seo-jun's.
I am happy.
I got such a beautiful son for free.
Look, Mom.
Look.
Mom, I won.
Gosh, such a handsome boy.
Whose grandson is he?
Right?
Isn't he cute? He's your grandson.
Yes, he's very cute.
Did you like the food?
It was delicious.
She'd never say that it was bad.
You invited her home to serve her food.
Where are you going? We aren't done yet.
I'm going to take some of my stuff.
Why don't you move back in?
Don't say something so horrible.
Call me when he's done nagging.
I thought that he was grown up,
but he's far from it.
How is he doing these days?
He's doing better than you imagine.
You worked hard turning him into an adult.
See? Wasn't I right?
I picked you as soon as I saw you
at the mentor meeting.
Are you still sponsoring college students?
What's the point of earning money?
It's best to support those
who have potential.
I can't find any.
There's no one as good as you are.
It won't be easy to find.
How much longer do I have to
keep inviting you to come here?
Is Jeong-hoon not good enough for you yet?
Now that he's grown up,
you should move in together.
I got ahead of myself again.
Have your tea.
Did my father say something to you again?
You look a bit down.
Is he going to pull out his investment?
If he does, it would be his loss.
I knew it. That's Kang Ji-yun.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Don't worry. I'm strong.
Then why did you pass out
from overworking?
Seriously, be careful.
I'm just concerned.
I know. I won't overdo it.
Are you worrying about me?
Woo Jeong-hoon, you're all grown up.
When was the first time I saw you
at the society meeting?
Wasn't it before you even graduated
high school?
It would be problematic
if you still see me as a kid.
Look.
Don't I look more handsome up close?
Don't do this anywhere else.
Come on, what's the hold up?
Let's go, Mr. Woo.
Mr. Woo?
Hello.
Aren't you the CEO of Peoplez?
From the eighth floor.
Yes.
Mr. Yu brags about you a lot.
He says that you're very famous
and competent.
I thought that you were just pretty,
but you're also capable. I'm so jealous.
Here, this is for you.
Have a good day.
HEALTHY VEGETABLE JUICE
Come in.
It's your schedule this week.
Why do you have so much vegetable juice?
I heard that it's healthy.
Before my meeting with Mr. Jang,
- could you prepare--
- Excuse me for a moment.
Before your meeting with Mr. Jang,
I'm double-checking
the interview content with Mr. Kim.
Once it gets ready, I'll bring it to you.
You made a good choice.
Eat lots of that healthy stuff.
Are you going to Mr. Yu's
welcoming party tonight?
You think I dressed up for nothing?
The seat on Mr. Yu's right is
mine tonight.
I heard that many people
will be there at the party.
Unfortunately, people recognize
how handsome he is.
You'd better pull for me tonight.
Got it.
- Shall we go?
- Okay.
I can't wait.
Instead of working,
they spend energy on useless things.
Mr. Yu.
- Could you open this for me?
- Sure.
- Isn't it hard to open?
- Yes.
Here you go.
Ms. Kang, do you need anything?
No.
This is for you.
Come with us to the third round.
Okay.
- Thank you for the drink.
- That's a promise.
Well, isn't he excited?
Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu!
What?
Did everyone leave already?
All right!
Check this out!
Attention, everyone!
Could you be quiet?
- Seriously.
- I'm sorry.
All the players are ready.
Players, you're ready to dive in.
Here they come.
- Dive!
- One, two, three.
Dive!
They're in!
Let's drink.
- Cheers.
- Thank you for the drink.
- Have a drink.
- Cheers.
- Kyung…
Here you go. Drink up.
Come on, have a drink.
That's mine. All right.
All right now!
Attention, everyone.
Today is Mr. Yu's welcoming party.
And to promote amity
among everyone at Peoplez,
we're holding this special party.
Don't even think about going home alive.
I'm unzipping it.
She's really prepping herself!
Is everyone ready to drink?
- Yes!
Ms. Seo, you're determined
to drink tonight.
Everyone.
As I'm occupied with work
and private life,
I won't be able to drink
with you until the end.
- Boo.
- Come on.
However, as I recognize
the virtue of being a boss,
I will treat you here tonight!
Praise be!
- Bon appétit.
- I will.
Thank you!
We'll order everything on the menu.
Feel free!
- Kyung-hwa, shall we?
- Cheers.
All right, Ms. Seo.
- Come on.
- Goodness.
- All right. Tonight,
- This is really good.
It's my treat, especially
because of Mr. Yu who's busy these days.
So Mr. Yu, please get intoxicated.
Let's hear a word from Mr. Yu.
- Good luck.
- You can do it.
Well,
thank you very much for coming
to my welcoming party.
Everyone at Peoplez have been kind to me,
especially Mr. Kim Young-soo.
He has been so kind to me.
Could I ask you to make a toast?
- No, no…
- Thank you!
A toast? No way.
Just do it.
- It's okay.
- Come on!
- When it comes to this, you're the best.
- You gotta do it.
I'm the best?
You should've told me.
If so, I should do it.
I didn't know I was the best.
I don't have anything
to say in particular.
Okay.
Octopus. Let's go with "octopus."
- "Oc."
- Occasions like today…
- "To."
- Totally requires me to…
- "Pus."
- Push your buttons!
Octopus!
Ha!
"Ha?"
Ha! That's funny.
- Did you just laugh?
- Hilarious. Cheers!
- That's it! Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
- Octopus, right?
- I've noticed it for a long time.
Your sense of humor isn't
exactly classy, with all honesty.
- If that made you laugh.
- Wasn't it funny?
- Exactly what part?
- Octopus.
Oh, don't push it.
Right, don't Kyung-hwa and Mr. Kim
have a similar sense of humor?
That's right.
So you should make up already.
It's unbearable to be walking
on eggshells around you.
- He's right.
- Seriously.
We never made you walk on eggshells.
What's there to make up for?
These things can happen from time to time.
Don't you agree?
Yes, I agree.
Right.
Okay.
Shall we lighten up and have a drink?
- That sounds great.
- Good idea!
There's nothing wrong between us.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim!
Moving on,
I'll make sure to report to you.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Let's get along.
That's octopus for ya!
- Let's octopush it!
- Octopus it is!
Octopus!
- Octopus!
We're all octopus!
The boss does all the work.
Is this a social club or something?
They don't even work.
MESSAGES
Are you still at work?
Don't skip dinner.
Call me if you need anything.
Just in case,
here's the address to the party.
Join us whenever you change your mind.
I'll be waiting.
Byeol, what did you eat?
You had pasta?
Was it good?
Hold on.
Mr. Woo, are you leaving?
Hey, Mr. Yu.
Yes, I have something important,
so I'm disappearing.
- Have a good evening.
- You too!
What Auntie made couldn't have been good.
It sounds like someone is talking
about me behind my back.
Were you listening?
Come on, my cooking has gotten better.
All right.
I'm sorry about tonight.
I'll take care of the kids this weekend.
It's fine. We're close enough for that.
You haven't had a company dinner
in forever. Enjoy yourself.
I won't be late. Thank you.
Okay, but don't drink too much.
Bye.
All right.
We're close enough for that.
Mom, are you hot?
What?
You're blushing.
Me? You're right.
It must be hot in the house.
Kids!
Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu?
Mr. Yu Eun-ho.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You came.
- Should I tell…
- What?
Isn't that Mr. Yu and Ms. Kang?
No way. Ms. Kang wouldn't be…
- It's them.
- Hey, Ji-yun!
My goodness.
Are you here to see me? Are you?
- Ms. Kang!
- I can't believe it.
I've been looking for you.
Here are your things.
We're going to the second round.
- Kang Ji-yun!
- Let's go.
We should go.
- Second round.
- We should all go.
Kang Ji-yun.
Ms. Kang.
What?
She's not here.
I thought she'd be here alone.
I just missed her.
I don't love you
There's no other reason
- I don't want to say sorry
- Sorry!
- -I don't want to ask
- Ask!
- For forgiveness
- Forgiveness
There was a reason why.
This is why I hate company dinners.
That is all…
Hey, Ms. Kang.
I can't believe that you actually came!
Good girl.
Since this is very rare…
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Line up if you want to drink
with Ms. Kang.
This is a rare chance.
- I'm up for it.
- Thank you so much.
Line up here.
- Take a seat.
- I feel honored.
Ms. Kang, I know I disappointed you.
- Apologize.
- I'll clink glasses.
Thank you.
Come on over.
This is your chance.
It's rare.
- I'll work harder.
- Please remember me.
- Ms. Kang!
- Thank you, Ms. Kang!
You should join us often.
Cheers.
It's not coming out.
Where is…
Cheers.
Did he hurt your feelings?
To me…
Candidates aren't the only problem.
You got it wrong.
When I recommend a promising candidate,
she says no.
When I recommend another good one,
she says no again.
She brings up all possible excuses
to reject them.
So I tried to find out.
You know what I found?
What?
The person in charge
didn't want any candidate
who's more educated than her.
I almost cursed.
Is she kidding me?
That's wrong.
Our Mr. Yu.
Take our kind and handsome Mr. Yu.
Things weren't like that at HR, right?
- Mr. Kim, that department is…
- Right?
- …completely different from ours.
- Mr. Yu.
We can't compare them.
I like it when you smile
Mr. Yu!
Yes?
Never mind. Just drink.
- Just drink.
- Don't mind him.
- Drink.
- We're talking about life.
- Jeez.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay even if I'm alone!
As long as I can see you…
Kyung-hwa, we should…
- Kyu.
- It's Kyung. Let's do it.
Let's do it.
- I love parties like this.
- Really?
- I don't spend anything.
- Oh, gosh.
- We're leaving.
- We're off.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Goodbye.
- Let's go to the third round.
Are you going to another bar?
The third round?
- Octopus. Octopus!
- Round three?
Stay here for a minute.
I'll take you home.
Mr. Driver, where are you?
Okay.
Thank you.
Get in.
Take her as far as you go. Thank you.
- What? No.
- Can you go in?
Where do you think--
Mr. Kim gave us money for another round.
- Goodbye.
- Kyung-hwa.
- Bye.
- Get home safe.
Mr. Kim looks a little sad, so be careful.
Goodbye.
Kyung-hwa.
Wait.
Yes, Mr. Kim?
You had it hard with Mr. Park, didn't you?
Me too.
He's a good man,
but he's very indecisive.
Last time, he couldn't make up his mind
until the last moment.
What is there to think about?
It wasn't because of you.
That's just how he is,
so don't worry about it.
I think
I was being greedy.
You should have…
No, that's enough.
He's your candidate.
Just make the project successful.
Be confident.
You're doing a good job.
See you tomorrow.
Get home safe, sir.
Everyone went to the third round,
but I didn't join them.
Hurry up. Okay.
See you.
Have you seen Ms. Kang?
Ji-yun?
Did she disappear?
Don't worry. She went to the office.
The office?
Going home instinctively.
I mean, going to work instinctively.
Whenever she gets drunk,
she goes to the office.
You'll find her alive tomorrow morning.
Don't worry and go home.
Hey, Kang-seok!
Hey, you're here too.
Why did you drink so much?
I didn't drink too much.
- Let's see.
- Hold me.
- Did something good happen?
- Yes.
I had fun today.
- Kang Ji-yun was here tonight.
- She was?
See you.
We did drink a lot.
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang?
I should be taking her home.
Mr. Yu…
You're handsome.
Yu Eun-ho.
Was that a dream?
Did it really happen?
After the company party,
- you didn't return to the office?
- No.
Weren't you the one
who called me Father last time? Right?
I'm sorry about that.
Can you sleep without
- your parents tonight?
- See you tomorrow, Dad.
We're meeting at Eun-ho's house.
Everyone has to be there.
Ms. Kang?
Is no one else here?
It got canceled because no one could come.
Ms. Kang!
Yes?
Would you like to have dinner?
On the day of our company party.
Why did you pretend not to remember?
How much do you remember?
How much do you want me to remember?
Subtitle translation by Helena Noh